Up to 2.5 dimensions Oh, that's my current favorite story.
2.5次元まで あ ら、今のお気に入りの話だよ
What should I do?
どうすればいいんだろう?
Try opening your legs.
足を開けてみてください
Can you be safe in an instant?
一瞬で無事になれる?
Open your shirt and have a brownie.
ワイシャツ開けてブラウニーして
Shall I open all my shirts?
ワイシャツ全部開けちゃおうか
With the legs like before, like this,
さっきみたいな足をこうやって、
Try opening your legs.
足 を開けてみてください
Buy skirt makeup and make brownies.
スカートメイクを買ってブラウニーして
I became safe in an instant,
一瞬で無事になって、
Spread your legs and have a brownie.
足 を開けてブラウニーして
Just in baht.
バーツで一応
Stretch your legs, stretch your legs.
足を伸ばして、足を伸ばして
Close your legs.
足を閉じて
Open your butt and close your legs.
お尻を開けて、足を閉じて
close your legs
足を閉じ
hand.
て
It feels good.
気 持ちいい
Open your legs, close your legs.
足を開けて、足を閉じて
Open your legs,
足を開けて、
Close your legs.
足 を閉じて
Open your legs, close your legs.
足を開けて、足を閉じて
Open your legs and close your legs.
足 を 開けて、足を閉じて
Open your legs, close your legs.
足を開けて、足を閉じて
Feels good.
気持ちいい